import { Component } from '@angular/core';

@Component({
  selector: 'app-loan-against-property',
  templateUrl: './loan-against-property.component.html',
  styleUrls: ['./loan-against-property.component.scss']
})
export class LoanAgainstPropertyComponent {

  selectedFaq : number = -1
  loanAgainstPropertyFaqs: any = [
    {
      question: "Will I get a loan against my property?",
      answer: "Yes, you can get a loan against property if the property is registered in your name and you have the required set of documents. Additionally, you must be eligible to secure a loan against property.",
    },
    {
      question: "Is it possible to apply for a loan against property if it is a joint property?",
      answer: "Yes, it is possible to apply for a loan against property in the case of joint property. The co-owner of the property will become the co-applicant in the loan application. Additionally, the chances of securing a higher loan amount also increase.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is eligibility for a loan against property?",
      answer: "The loan against property eligibility criteria is quite simple. You must be between the ages of 21 and 65, have a yearly income of INR35,000, a good credit history, and the property must be registered in your name.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the maximum term for which I can avail of a loan against property (LAP)?",
      answer: "You can avail of a loan against property (LAP) for a maximum of 20 years.",
    },
    {
      question: "Is there an application fee for a loan against property?",
      answer: "Yes, to avail of a loan against property, you need to pay an application fee of 1 percent of the loan amount plus applicable service tax.",
    },
    {
      question: "How will I know if my Loan Against Property application is approved?",
      answer: "On the approval of your loan application, the designated bank executive will get in touch with you for further processing. Additionally, you can check your loan status by visiting the bankâ€™s official website.",
    },
    {
      question: "Is the interest rate for the loan against property standards between lenders?",
      answer: "No, interest rates vary from one lender to another based upon certain factors, such as credit history, loan tenure, income stability, location of the property, and much more.",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the maximum loan amount that I can avail of against the property?",
      answer: "You can borrow up to INR 7 crores against a property. However, the loan amount depends upon the market value of the property.",
    },
    {
      question: "Can I get a loan against a plot?",
      answer: "Yes, you can get a loan against a plot, residential property and commercial property.",
    },
    {
      question: "Can a loan against property be availed without income proof?",
      answer: "Yes, you can get a loan against property without income proof, but you will have to submit other required documents.",
    },
    {
      question: "Can a loan against property be availed without CIBIL?",
      answer: "Banks take the CIBIL score into consideration for evaluating a loan application. If you have bad credit, either your loan application will be rejected, or you will have to pay higher loan interest rates for it.",
    },
  ];

  handleSelectedFaq(index: number){
    if(index === this.selectedFaq){
      this.selectedFaq = -1;
      return;
    }else{
      this.selectedFaq = index
    }
  }
}
